Railway Labor Executives' Association Additional Records 5552
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Government. Federal Housing Administration, Low Income Housing., 1968 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  H.U.D. pamphlets on low income housing, housing discrimination, and housing for the elderly and handicapped. Plans by RLEA to sponsor the construction of low-cost apartments for tax benefits.
- RLEA. General, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  Correspondence
- RLEA. Emergency Relief Fund, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- RLEA. AFL-CIO, Speakers' Bureau, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- RLEA. Constitution and By-Laws, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- RLEA. Travelers' Insurance Policy, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- RLEA. American Railway Supervisors Association, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  Correspondence.
- RLEA. American Train Dispatchers' Association, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  Correspondence. Contains copy of ICC's Accident Report No. 4098.
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  Correspondence file. Primary correspondent is H.E. Gilbert, president, BLFE. Also includes BLFE agreements, reports, and a copy of the Federal Hours of Service Act.
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  Correspondence. Includes BRT comic book about local union elections: "Cliff Merritt and the Very Candid Candidate."
- RLEA. Brotherhood Railway Carmen of America, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Conference on Public Transportation, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  Extracts from pre-conference papers
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Railway Clerks (BRAC), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Correspondence. Includes list of all Sick Leave Agreements BRAC has with different carriers, a pamphlet "A Proposal merger of BRAC and TCU" in English and French, and a pamphlet containing an index of all Vacation Agreements.
- RLEA. BRAC. Youngdahl Decision, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- RLEA. Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- RLEA. Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders' International Union, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- RLEA. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- RLEA. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers and Blacksmiths, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- RLEA. International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- RLEA. International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- RLEA. International Organization of Masters, Mates, and Pilots of America, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- RLEA. National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- RLEA. Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- RLEA. Railroad Yardmasters of America, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- RLEA. Railway Employes' Department, AFL-CIO, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Correspondence and pamphlet "Official Proceedings of the 14th Convention of the Railway Employes' Department."
- RLEA. Sheet Metal Workers International Association, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- RLEA. Switchmen's Union of North America, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Correspondence and Mediation Agreement
- RLEA. Transportation Communication Employes Union, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Correspondence and pamphlet "Report of Proceeding of the 37th Regular and 4th Quadrennial Session of the Grand Division" in English and French.
- RLEA. Seafarers' International Union of North America, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- RLEA. Unification Agreement between ORCB, BLFE, BRT, and SUNA, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Creation of the United Transportation Union (UTU).
- RLEA. Canadian RLEA, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- RLEA. RLEA Meetings - General, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- RLEA. Monthly Meeting, Hamilton Hotel, Washington D.C., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- RLEA. Monthly Meeting, Miami, February, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Correspondence, planning documents, and bills. Also contains hotel brochures for various high-end Miami Beach hotel/convention centers.
- RLEA. Meeting Chicago, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  Crossed out from title: "April 23rd. LaSalle Hotel". Handwritten on title: "Cancelled. Held Hamilton Hotel - March 19."
- RLEA. Meeting Agendas, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- RLEA. Reports of Counsel, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- RLEA. Assessments, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- RLEA. Applications for Affiliation, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Judicial. Court Cases - General, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  Contains newspaper clippings, Amicus Briefs filed by the RLEA, and filings in re featherbedding issues.
- RLEA. 1961 Wages and Rules - General, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  Contains newspaper clippings in re crew consist and featherbedding disputes.
- RLEA. Southern Rules Movement, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- RLEA. Job Stabilization Movement on the Missouri-Kansas-Texas Railroad, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- RLEA. Wage and Rules Movement, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- RLEA. Radio-Telephone Equipment Communications, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  Use of radio communication in railroad operations; operations rule changes.
- RLEA. 1962 Rules Movement, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- RLEA. Chicago and Illinois Midland Railway. Section 6 Notices, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- RLEA. Florida East Coast Railway, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  Rules dispute between non-operating employees and FEC Railway
- RLEA. Louisville and Nashville 'No Injury' Reports, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- RLEA. 1963 Wage and Rules Movement, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- RLEA. Changes in Discipline Policy and Procedures, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- RLEA. Employment and Medical Examination Policy and Procedures, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- RLEA. NW Railway's Thrift Plan for Non-Union Employees, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- RLEA. Compulsory Retirement, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- RLEA. 1966 Wage-Rules Movement, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  Railway Employes' Department, AFL-CIO
- RLEA. 1967 Wage-Rules Movement Guaranteed Annual Wage, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- RLEA. Thrift Plan Penn Central, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- RLEA. 1968 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 2, Folder 46)
- RLEA. Health and Welfare, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  In re GA 23111, GA 23000. Travelers' Insurance and benefits in case of strikes and lockouts.
- RLEA. Travelers' Insurance Group Policy GA-23111 [folder 1 of 2], 1968 (Box 2, Folder 48a)
- RLEA. Travelers' Insurance Group Policy GA-23111[folder 2 of 2], 1968 (Box 2, Folder 48b)
  Includes Agreement with covering employers.
- RLEA. Travelers' Insurance Company, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  Group policy information
- RLEA. Operating Unions, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  Local Travelers' Insurance plans
- RLEA. Rules Committee, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- RLEA. Carrier Strike Insurance Program, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- RLEA. Automation, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- RLEA. Union Shop - General, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- RLEA. Union Dues - General, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- RLEA. Diversification of Railroads - "Piggybacking", 1968 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- RLEA. Permits on Railroad Property for Union Business, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- RLEA. Railway Labor, Railway Building Funds, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- RLEA. Committees, General, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- RLEA. Safety Committee, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- RLEA. Committee to Study Railroad Mergers, Consolidations, Etc., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- RLEA. Committee to Meet with Association of American Railroads, Labor Management Relations Committee, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- RLEA. Political Education Committee, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- RLEA. Committee on Railroad Retirement, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- RLEA. Legislative Representatives, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- RLEA. Employee Passes, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- RLEA. Personnel Records, General, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- RLEA. Prospective Employees, General, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  RESTRICTED
- RLEA. Department of Research and Education, Misc. Requests, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- RLEA. Government Printing Office, Account No. 11256, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- RLEA. Insurance - General, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- RLEA. Postage Meter, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 72)
- RLEA. Addressograph-Multigraph Corporation, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- RLEA. Office Equipment - General, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- RLEA. The Thero-Fax Copying Machine, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 75)
- RLEA. Office Furniture, General, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 76)
- RLEA. Lawyers - General, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 77)
- RLEA. Lawyers Bills [folder 1 of 3], 1968 (Box 3, Folder 1a)
  Bills invoiced by legal matter.
- RLEA. Lawyers Bills [folder 2 of 3], 1968 (Box 3, Folder 1b)
- RLEA. Lawyers Bills [folder 3 of 3], 1968 (Box 3, Folder 1c)
- RLEA. Strikes, General, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- RLEA. Florida East Coast Railway Strike, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  By Shop Craft employees.
- RLEA. Atlanta Joint Terminal Employee Protection, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  In event of merger with Louisville and Nashville Railroad
- RLEA. Shop Crafts Dispute, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Legislation. Interstate Commerce Act, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Interstate Commerce Commission Emergency Panning and Operation Manual
- Legislation. Feasibility Study for a Wheel-Rail Dynamics Research Facility, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 7a)
  Department of Transportation publication
- Legislation. Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 7b)
  In re amendments to Railroad Retirement Act
- Legislation. Railroad Safety Legislation [folder 1 of 3], 1968 (Box 3, Folder 8a)
  Proposed legislation, correspondence, lobbying efforts, Senate testimony, research and reports.
- Legislation. Railroad Safety Legislation [folder 2 of 3], 1968 (Box 3, Folder 8b)
- Legislation. Railroad Safety Legislation [folder 3 of 3], 1968 (Box 3, Folder 8c)
- Legislation. Bills to Amend Railroad Retirement Act [folder 1 of 2], 1968 (Box 3, Folder 9a)
  Includes transcript of proceedings before House Committee
- Legislation. Bills to Amend Railroad Retirement Act [folder 2 of 2], 1968 (Box 3, Folder 9b)
- Legislation. Canadian Anti-Labor Legislation, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Legislation. PL 89-236 (Migratory Farm Labor) Canadian Situation, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Legislation. Depressed Areas, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Legislation. Minimum Wage Legislation, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Legislation. Hours of Service Law Amendments, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Legislation. Clayton Act Amendments, Rail Mergers Moratorium, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Legislation. Congressional Investigation of Railroads' Financial Condition, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Legislation. Conservation Legislation - Interior Department, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Legislation. Railroad Retirement Act, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  Drafts of amendments, lobbying by RLEA, drafts of instructional pamphlets and reports
- Legislation. "Super Grades," H.R. 7377 and S. 1732 (1961), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Bank Holding Company Act amendment
- Legislation. Department of Transportation (DOT), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Legislation. Department of Transportation, Appropriations, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Legislation. Surcharge Tax Proposal - 1967, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Legislation. 1968 Endorsements, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  Contains several newspaper clippings, letters from Ladies' Auxiliaries about supposed endorsements of candidates, endorsements by member unions, broadsides, bulletins, report of RLEA Endorsements Advisory Committee, and get out the vote efforts.
- Legislation. Railroad Safety Legislation, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  Includes pamphlet "Toll of Train and Train-Service Accidents" in Alabama.
- Legislation. Railroad Safety Legislation [folder 1 of 2], 1968 (Box 3, Folder 25a)
  Reports of proceedings of the Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce and testimony in re proposed legislation.
- Legislation. Railroad Safety Legislation [folder 2 of 2], 1968 (Box 3, Folder 25b)
- Legislation. Railroad Safety Legislation, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  Includes drafts of pamphlet "Toll of Train and Train-Service Accidents" with data for each state based on ICC figures. Contains computer punch taped labeled "house commerce," containing accident data.
- Legislation. Railroad Safety Legislation, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  Contains computer punch tape labeled "SC" on original folder and letters to members of Safety Committee.
- Government. DOT Rules, Standards and Instructions Cases - Approval of Changes in Signal Installation BS [folder 2 of 3], 1968 (Box 3, Folder 28b)
  DOT Public Notices
- RLEA. Office File Guides, 1967-1972 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Indexes to the files of the RLEA for 1967 through 1972.
- Government. Executive Branch, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  In re appointments to the Pan American Railway Congress.
- Government. House and Senate, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Government. Constitution, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Government. Congressional Campaign Contribution Requests, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Government. Appointment of Federal Judgeships, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Government. State Department, General, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Contains Sate Department publications "The Country Team: An Illustrated Profile of Our American Missions Abroad" (1967) and "Annual Report to Congress on the International Educational and Cultural Exchange Program for FY 1966."
- Government. State Department A.I.D. - John K. Meskimen, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  India Railroad management study.
- Government. Pan American Railway Congress, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Contains documents, pamphlets, booklets, and one invitation that are written in, or are partially written in, Spanish. Almost all documents in the folder are about Argentina.
- Government. U.S. National Commission in the Pan American Railway Congress Association, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Contains some documents and correspondences in Spanish
- Government. Payroll Savings Decision, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Government. Office of Emergency Planning, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Government. Labor-Management Manpower Policy Committee, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Drafts of Wage Stabilization Plan.
- Government. Regional Manpower Policy Committee, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Government. National Defense Executive Reserves, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Government. Department of Transportation (DOT), 1968 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Federal Railroad Administration bulletins
- Government. DOT, High Speed Ground Transportation, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  Includes promotional materials for a high speed train along the Northeast Corridor
- Government. DOT, Membership and Staff Appointments, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Government. National Transportation Safety Board, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  Includes NTSB report on accident involving collision of SP freight train with a passenger car in Sacramento, CA.
- Government. Railroad Safety Board, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Government. Federal Railroad Administration, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  Includes RLEA's comments on FRA Docket No. 1, "Procedures for Prescribing Regulations."
- Government. Accident Reports, DOT Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 2], 1968 (Box 4, Folder 21a)
- Government. Accident Reports, DOT, Miscellaneous [folder 2 of 2], 1968 (Box 4, Folder 21b)
- Government. DOT Rules, Standards and Instructions re Signal Systems [folder 1 of 2], 1968 (Box 4, Folder 22a)
  DOT Public Notices. Also includes submission by the Reading Co. to install a traffic control system. Submission contains schematics for system.
- Government. DOT Rules, Standards and Instructions re Signal Systems [folder 2 of 2], 1968 (Box 4, Folder 22b)
- Government. DOT Rules, Standards and Instructions Cases - Approval of Changes in Signal Installation BS [folder 1 of 3], 1968 (Box 4, Folder 23a)
- Government. DOT Rules, Standards and Instructions Cases - Approval of Changes in Signal Installation BS [folder 3 of 3], 1968 (Box 4, Folder 23c)
- Government. DOT Rules, Standards and Instructions Cases [folder 1 of 3], 1968 (Box 4, Folder 24a)
- Government. DOT Rules, Standards and Instructions Cases [folder 2 of 3], 1968 (Box 4, Folder 24b)
- Government. DOT Rules, Standards and Instructions Cases [folder 3 of 3], 1968 (Box 4, Folder 24c)
- Government. DOT Bureau of Locomotive Inspection General, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Rules for inspection and testing of multiple unit engine
- Government. DOT Power Brakes, Rules and Standards for, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Government. DOT and ICC Safety Dockets, General, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Government. DOT Application Of Safety Appliance Acts to Track Motor, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Government. DOT Prevention of Railway Highway Grade Crossing Accidents, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Includes multiple NTSB accident reports
- Government. Labor Department - General, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Government. Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Includes report on Labor Developments Abroad
- Government. BLS - Wage Chronology #40 - Non Operating Employes, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Government. Bureau of Labor Standards, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Government. Bureau of Labor-Management Reports, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  No records contained in folder at delivery.
- Government. Interstate Commerce Commission, General, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  ICC bulletins. Includes ICC requirement for inclusion of the New Haven into Penn Central merger.
- Government. ICC Membership and Staff Appointment, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Government. ICC Rules of Practice and Administrative Procedure, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Government. ICC Statistics, M-300 Reports, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Government. ICC Proposed New Classification of Class 1 and 2 Railroads, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Government. ICC M-400 Accidents - Summary of, Etc., 1968 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Government. ICC Statistics - Accidents Reports - Form I, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Government. ICC Statistics - Carriers Monthly Hours of Service Report, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Government. ICC Statistics 230 Fuel and Power for Locomotive, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Government. ICC Statistics 240 Motive Power and Car Equipment, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Government. ICC Statistics 100-159 Operating Revenues and Expenses, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Government. ICC Statistics 200 Operating Statistics of Large Steam Railways, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Government. ICC Statistics 250 Passenger Traffic, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Government. ICC Statistics 220 Revenue Traffic, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Government. ICC Statistics 125 Selected Income and Balance Sheets 106:3-12, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Government. ICC Statistics 300-350 Steam Railways, Class I Wages, Monthly 1968 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Government. ICC Statistics 210 Train and Yard Service (Replaces Disc. Reports), 1968 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Government. ICC Statistics Q-950 Revenues, Expenses and Statistics on Freight Forwarders, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Government. ICC Statistics 2-650 Revenues and Traffics of Class A and B, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Government. ICC Accounting Rules, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Government. ICC Rules for Reporting Accidents, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Government. Reports Forms - ICC Accidents Reports, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Government. Designation of Persons to Examine Reports of Accidents, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Government. Bureau of Transport Economics and Statistics - General, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Government. Rules for Reporting of Wages and Hours, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Government. Railroad Service Board, Bureau of Safety and Service - General, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Government. National Mediation Board, Membership and Staff Appointments, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Government. National Mediation Board, General, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  Pending cases
- Government. National Mediation Board, Public Law Board Decisions on Procedural Questions [folder 1 of 3], 1968 (Box 5, Folder 39a)
  Bulletins
- Government. National Mediation Board, Public Law Board Decisions on Procedural Questions [folder 2 of 3], 1968 (Box 5, Folder 39b)
- Government. National Mediation Board, Public Law Board Decisions on Procedural Questions [folder 3 of 3], 1968 (Box 5, Folder 39c)
- Government. National Mediation Board, Rules of Procedure and Administration, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Government. National Mediation Board, Amendments re Individuals as Bargaining Agents, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Government. National Mediation Board, Appropriations, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Government. National Mediation Board, Lists of Carriers and Designated Officers to Handle Dispute, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Government. National Mediation Board, Decisions and Certifications, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  Of special and emergency boards
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board - General, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board. First Division, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board. Second Davison, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board. Third Division, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board. Fourth Division, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board, Organizations Qualified to Participate in Selection Members, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board. Membership, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board. Application of Awards, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board. Awards adopting Gunther Decision, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Government. National Railroad Adjustment Board. Third Party Notices, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- RLEA. United Farm Workers Strike, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Contains a newspaper clippings about grape vineyards strike.
- RLEA. Los Angeles Herald-Examiner Strike-Lockout, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Contains newspaper clippings.
- RLEA. Contracting Out, General, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- RLEA. Contracting Out, Federal Law, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- RLEA. Contracting Out, Post Office, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Railroads. Railroads - General, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Contains newspaper clippings, also general mailers from carriers, information on regulations, and a pamphlet celebrating the 100th Anniversary of the Santa Fe Railroad.
- Railroads. Railroad Ownership, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Contains newspaper clippings, statistical reports, and bulletins.
- Railroads. Penn Central, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Railroads. Association of American Railroads, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Railroads. Association of American Railroads - Highway User Charges, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Railroads. Association of Western Railways, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Contains clipping and pamphlets in re Grade Crossing Safety Concerns
- Railroads. National Railway Labor Conference, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Railroads. Hospital Associations, General, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  Includes pamphlet "By-Laws of the Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Employes' Hospital Association."
- Railroads. Hospital Associations, Kansas City Southern, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Railroads. Hospital Associations, Missouri Pacific, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Railroads. Hospital Associations, Illinois Central, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Railroads. Tuition Aid Program - Union Pacific Railroad, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Railroads. Western and Atlantic, Proposed Lease by Southern Railway, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Other Organizations. COPE, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO Legislative Action Bulletin, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO, Executive Council, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  Pamphlet "Goals for Teachers' Salaries in Our Public Schools" by Leon Keyserling
- Other Organizations. AFL-CIO - General, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 22)